

CONTACT ME



+91 987.3258.203



hello@angadluthra.me



/angadsinghluthra



www.angadluthra.me

ABOUTME

A student entrepreneur, currently running a design firm with work experience in web development, management and online journalism.

Have demonstrated interests in music instruments, pottery, robotics and creative use of IT platforms, such as Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.

Always intrigued by and attracted to the confluence of art and technology with any opportunity to bring in creativity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015 - 2018 Co-Founder & Designer, Nuked Studios

I currently run and manage a graphic and website development frim with a partner. This venture has allowed me to experience the industry and its daily work.

2014 - 2016 Lead Designer, Y E S Pvt. Ltd.

Involved in managing and hosting the company's website as well as handling all design and Information Technology related solutions.

2014 - 2016 Partner, Amalgamated.Co

Created online website and app. Hold 40% stakes in the online magazine and journal and write for the technology sectionas well.

JAN 2014 Intern, Photographer

Assisted a reputated photographer, Sumiko Murgai Nanda, on a couple of projects.

X AWARDS & RECOGNITION

Karamveer Chakra and Fellowship / March 2015

Acknowledged by the International Confederation of NGO's - ICONGO in association with the United Nations – For Entrepreneurship & Technology

Featured in Print & Web Magazine / January 2015

Inkspire - Featured in an art magazine, on behalf of Nuked Studios.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2018 Srishti Insitute of Art, Design & Technology

Currently pursuing a degree in Graphic Design and Art Practices from the institute. I wish to further pursue a masters in the same.

2013 - 2015 Vasant Valley School

I graduated high school in 2015, with a percentage of 93.5 % in the CBSE Board Examinations.



